Illia Cheshkov

♥ Rieti, Italy ■ cheshkov.ilya@gmail.com 🛘 +393203428611 🛅 in/ilyacheshkov

SUMMARY

I am passionate about Information Technologies and Software Testing.

Graduated in Computer Science with a Master's degree, I have a work experience of 16 years in computer field, of which almost 9 as a Programmer Engineer.

I am a responsible person, precise, fast in learning, oriented to the result, with teamworking and problem solving.

I speak English fluently and have a knowledge of the Italian language, I am rapidly improving through practice and in-depth courses.

I have advanced knowledge of operating systems and of the hardware.

I have gained specialized skills in bug tracking systems, in content management systems and testing and development tools.

I am interested in working in the IT industry, especially in QA Software Tester role.

EXPERIENCE

Software Tester

Powaertime

March 2022 - September 2022, Ukraine, remote

- · Executing manual and automated test for web and mobile application
- · Created and executed test cases and check lists
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Collaborated with development team to identify and fix bugs

QA Tester

Skylex

· Manual testing of mobile application, writing and executing test cases

May 2022 - January 2023, remote

Engineer-programmer

Milandr

August 2013 - February 2022, Moscow, Russia

- · Development of programs and test solutions for digital integrated circuits with Advantest 93k test platforms.
- · Development of test programs with IMS and Labview test platforms

Support engineer

freelance, Internet provider

· Troubleshooting connectivity issues for customers who experience problems with their Internet service.

February 2009 - July 2012, Ukraine

System administrator

freelance, computer clubs

· Configured and maintained Windows-based networks and systems

January 2006 - February 2008, Ukraine

SKILLS

Windows, Linux, MacOS, MS Office Selenium IDE, Selenium WebDriver, TestNG, JUnit, DevTools, GIT Trello, Jira, Confluence Java, Python, HTML, CSS, MySQL

Ukrainian, Russian - mother tongue English - fluent, B2/C1 Italian - good, B1/B2

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science

Kyiv Polytechnic University · Kyiv, Ukraine · 2005

COURSEWORK

Corso di Lingua e Cultura Italiana (B2)

Randstad • 2023 • Italian

QA Automation Basics

 ${\tt RedRover\,School} \cdot {\tt 2022} \cdot {\tt software\,testing\,automation,\,java\,basics,\,selenium\,webdriver}$

Software Testing Introduction Course

EPAM · 2022 · software testing basics

Introduction to Software Testing

Coursera \cdot 2021 \cdot software testing

Python Basic Programming Course

Coursera · 2019 · python basics

V93000 SOC Basic User Training

Advantest Europe · 2013